PS hunting effort to make this cleanup
I'll see you
next
time.
Retreat! Retreat!
All Marines, evacuate!
Board your ships now!
Do you know what happened
at the center of the city?
No clue.
I'm just following orders.
St.
Saturn, Admiral Borsalino.
Please retreat. Hurry.
There's no time.
Kizaru and I will remain here.
Continue preparations without pause.
When you're through, commence bombardment.
Sir, you're sure?
Just go.
Yes sir you came to
kill me thought all
of this be over once you accomplish that?
Spare the island with or without me
egghead houses the latest research from
Every field of study in the world if
you burn it down you'll set scientific
progress back a century.
Revoke the Buster Call, now!
Please, Kizaru, help me.
What if there's something
else you're hiding from us?
Something troublesome for the government,
perhaps?
That is a risk we would be fools to take.
We do not need your progress. Yes,
I'm begging you on
behalf of all humanity.
Ah, there's something
I neglected to mention.
It's about that ship that
escaped the island yesterday.
I've issued an order to have it pursued.
After all,
there might be people on board who learn
something about the Void
Sentry in their town.
I must ensure that none of them survive.
So I sent a warship.
How could you do such a thing?
They don't know anything!
They're innocent civilians!
You are the one who got
them involved, Vegapunk.
You broke the law, just
as they did on Ohio.
You could not save your lust for knowledge,
so you dug too deep into the past.
As the beasts must remain on the
island, marines to your ships!
As soon as preparations are
complete, we'll commence our attack!
Ship 54, ready to fire!
Ship 21, ready to fire!
Awaiting orders!
Hurry!
Everyone in the vacuum rocket!
We don't know how long Vegapunk
will be able to distract them.
The meeting point is the rear
entrance of the Labophase.
Be ready, okay?
We'll leave as soon as everyone arrives!
I got it!
Sanji, what about Vegapunk?
Don't you worry, Bonnie.
I'll get him out of here no sweat.
Good luck, bro, and stay safe!
I'll be fine.
Hey, Nami, it's Sanji. What's your status?
We're already at the rear entrance.
What's all the noise down there?
Yeah, about that.
What?
Did you say Buster Call?
This island is the force!
One Buster Call was
already too much for me.
This isn't fair.
What's going to happen to Stella?
Okay, this is no time to
be freaking out, guys!
Stay calm like me and
we'll all just run away!
Stop, Robin!
Everything's fine.
You just keep resting, okay?
Sanji, where's Luffy?
Is he with you?
What about Franky and Bonnie?
Are they okay?
Luffy's fine and the rest are headed up.
What's your status over there?
Most of us are good, but Zoro's
still getting held up by Luchi.
Jinbei is heading there now to go get him.
No way Zoro's finding his
way back without an escort.
As for Brooke, he's supposed
to bring the Sunny around.
Lilith is there with him.
There's just one tiny problem.
We were going to have the Vega
Force One carry the ship away,
but that's not an option for us anymore.
Because Kizaru completely destroyed it.
Wait, then how are we supposed
to get off the island?
Well, I don't know, but
apparently Brooke has a plan.
Nothing like a piping hot cup of tea while
I effortlessly move our
ship over the island.
Am I good or what?
Not too shabby, Bones. Nice work.
At this rate, we'll hit the
rear entrance in no time at all.
Freezing the island clouds and letting the
ship slide on them was a work of genius.
Coming from the world's greatest genius,
I dare say, that is some high praise.
Damn, this is fun!
So, how are we gonna
stop when we get there?
You know, I haven't thought
about that part yet.
What?!
We're just gonna fall to our deaths!
Fix this right now!
I don't know how!
Help me, Lil' Head!
You better start thinking fast!
They still haven't brought
the Laplephase barrier down.
All ships, the target
is Egghead's urban area!
Concentrate fire on the central
factory and the future city.
Begin the bombardment!
Please wait!
We haven't got any seats yet!
The pacifists are firing! Run away!
Take it.
Preparing to depart febrile phase.
Destination Lobby phase.
Alright.
We're ready!
Vacuum rocket, go!
Let's do it!
That's what I call speed! Hell yeah!
Transit duration, 32 seconds.
Amano Murakumo, sword.
Damn it, Kizaru! Bonnie!
I'm on my way!
Pacifistas, fire on Bonnie and Kuma.
I want them dead.
Simply exquisite.
Kuma sacrificed everything
to save his daughter's life.
And now she'll be blown to
bits by one of his own clones.
Truly the height of fire.
I'll feed him in for an insect.
Dad, it's me!
Bonnie, when I heard that
you had become a pirate,
the first possible scenario
flashed through my mind.
I could not control what the
Navy did with the Pacifistas,
built in your father's likeness.
He could be forced to shoot his own daughter
without understanding what he'd done.
By me!
No more...
Hey, that's Straw Hat, right?
Oh no, no more moving, Gumbarf!
Capture him!
He's an emperor of the sea!
They failed to destroy the escape vessel.
Someone alert! Kizaru!
Tell him, our attackers,
they're coming to Akainu!
Looks like the battle's on.
Guess the newspaper had that part right.
Did he just digest all of that food?
If we get too close, he might eat us.
I thought he was human, but maybe not.
Incoming!
We gotta move.
The flames are closing in on us.
If we stay here, then
we're going down, too.
Attack on three!
He may be strong, but
we'll stop him with C.
Prism Stonecum.
One, two...
Run to the ship! Go! No!
I had it down, boy!
Start from the shore
and burn it down! Fire!
Hold on, Gomorrah! Bunny!
Atlas! Come in! I need your help!
Shoot that fool!
And his daughter, too!
Listen to me.
You must tell Bonnie.
I'm almost there!
Okay!
I'm on it!
Bonnie!
Atmos!
Dad!
Don't shoot!
It's me!
We need to escape from here!
Please help us!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Did you hear that voice? What?
How in the hell can you hear
anything in all this noise?
What are they doing?
Why'd they turn around?
All the precipices have gone wrong. No!
That single fear tugged at my mind.
Bonnie
I was so worried.
What if you were killed by your own father
and kuma it's too cruel thinking that you
might harm your daughter
with your own hands.
That was a tragedy I could
not allow no matter what.
The government didn't
know but I programmed
something into every one of these weapons.
with Kuma's face.
So take heart.
It doesn't matter if he's given a command
by the highest authority in the bird.
It doesn't matter if everyone
and everything is against him.
Bonnie, Kuma will always,
always be on your side.
I selfishly made my wish come true.
But I'm no fool.
I know how this would end.
Such decisions have
consequences after all.
They always do.
VEGAPUK!
Dammit, no!
Kizaru, eliminate them immediately.
Kizaru! No!
This won't hurt, don't you worry.
We'll cut you both in half
nice and clean. Darn it.
Wait, Strava?
Where is he?
Ha-ha-ha!
Full belly, full power!
Ha-ha!
Now we're really having fun! Ha-ha!
Hey, Bonnie, you good?
Why is it bouncing like that?
Got a bigger issue!
I'm the path of faith!
VEGAPUNK!
Say something!
We gotta go! Come on!
You can't die here!
I know that rhythm.
Nika?
That's right.
Nika is my hero.
When Nika comes, he'll smile and
laugh, moving to this rhythm.
I see.
So you didn't realize the truth about him?
I couldn't be certain either,
till I saw it with my own eyes.
The very man Kuma placed his faith in,
Straw Hat moving, who he watched so
carefully, was Nika the sun gone all along.
Kuma had it right.
From the very start, the
Buster Call is futile.
Because there are people all over the
world who have been waiting for him.
They've waited for centuries.
Reporting from the northeast coast,
There is a massive ship approaching us!
It's them, without a doubt.
I thought they disbanded
over a hundred years ago.
Why are they here now?
Should we slow down? You kidding?
Keep her steady.
They're coming right toward us! Fire!
Damn it.
What the hell are the Giants doing here?
Oh, there they go again with
their why, why, why, Dory.
Don't they know everything that happens
in this world is inevitable, Froggy?
Don't worry, we're here
to back you up, Straw Hat.
Or should we call you Snake?
Emergency!
Agency, the giant pirates are here!
No, no,
no,
no.
Oh, my God.
No, I'm ready to go.
No, I'm ready to go. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Stop your job.
You're at home stage. Yeah.
Watch it, I go.
I'm getting no idea, it's like that thing.
I'm a lady. Do you do it for me?
MAD MAD MAD HE HAO UPI NIGHT!
I Saul NIGHT. I RECOGRAPHE?
IT IS A MONEY.
I'M GONNAGID!
LIKE A LIMA.